{
    "id": "b5e80d3d573145a5a5a573b881eaa7db",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I .................................. smoke, but now I don't.",
            "description": "We use ‘used to’ to talk about past habits.",
            "answers": [
                "used to",
                "am used to",
                "use to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................. me every day.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "visits",
                "is visiting",
                "visit"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ...................................... in a big city.",
            "description": "When you are not used to something, you are not familiar with it. Note that we use an –ing form after be + used to.",
            "answers": [
                "don't use to live",
                "am not used to live",
                "am not used to living"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... with old people.",
            "description": "When you are not used to something, you are not familiar with it. Note that we use an –ing form after be + used to.",
            "answers": [
                "used to working",
                "use to work",
                "am used to working"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is not ...................................... so much responsibility.",
            "description": "When you are not used to something, you are not familiar with it. Note that we use an –ing form after be + used to.",
            "answers": [
                "used to handle",
                "used to handling"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I won't allow .................................... in my house.",
            "description": "We use an ing form after allow if there is no object.",
            "answers": [
                "smoking",
                "to smoke",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like ....................................... a look at the house.",
            "description": "Would like is followed by to + infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "to take",
                "taking"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I feel like ...................................... to the beach.",
            "description": "Feel like is followed by an ing form. I feel like going means I would like to go.",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "to go",
                "going"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't feel like ................................... out with him.",
            "description": "Feel like is followed by an ing form. I don't feel like going means I don't want to go.",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "to go",
                "going"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I was about ................................... you.",
            "description": "This structure 'was about + to + infinitive' is used to say that you are going to do something at the moment or in the near future.",
            "answers": [
                "calling",
                "to call",
                "to calling"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn't mean .................................. you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "offending",
                "to offend",
                "to offending"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I would rather .............................. than .................................",
            "description": "I would rather is followed by an infinitive without to.",
            "answers": [
                "phone, write",
                "to phone, write",
                "to phone, writing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}